Ooooo! Uuhhh!
Why they tryna build a tower
and take all that is ours?
Leave us low down, hungry and devoured
Tried to silence me so
I'ma scream it louder
Tell me, is it for the money or the power?
Do you do it for the money or the power?
Time to pray, we gotta
all get on our knees
Ask the Lord to heal the
land of this disease
Flippin' tables in this
dirty den of thieves
I just wanna see us all live in peace
Tell me, is it for the money or the power?
Yeah! Och!
Did you do it for the money or the power?
It’s only us. Heh. Ayo!
Money and the power, man,
it's time, cause it's ours
I ain't sleepin', wide awake,
I see him movin' to devour
Takin' all our property,
board of games like Monopoly
Lord of Flames, I'm the prophecy,
lightin' up every block I see
Lord, I know I give em’ a lot
I'ma slow it down so you envision the plot
Stop and think before you acting
It's only real talk, we just not rappin'
I'ma give him passion, I'ma give him work
This love is everlasting,
I'ma take him to church
Put it in a caption so
you can read the verse
Lay not up for yourselves,
treasures upon the earth
Money or the power?
Do you do it for the money or the power?
Why they tryna build a tower
And take all of that is ours?
Leave us slowed down, hungry and devoured
Tried to silence me so
I'ma scream it louder
Tell me, is it for the money or the power?
Do you do it for the money or the power?
Time to pray, we gotta
all get on our knees
Ask the Lord to heal the
land of this disease
Flippin' tables in this
dirty den of thieves
I just wanna see us all live in peace
Tell me, is it for the money or the power?
Did you do it for the money or the power?
Ask what it costs, it costs a lot
I heard they tryna set
up shop on the block
They tryna take all that we got
I don't think they even care if we drop
Tell me how we got so far from the plot?
Wanna know, gotta ask,
gotta seek, gotta knock
I don't think they wanna
tell us what they know
They doin' it for show
It don't matter if you young or you old
If you rich or you poor
Choose now, will you stay or will you go?
So many paths, you gotta
choose the right road
Oh!
Why they tryna build a tower
And take all of that is ours?
Leave us low down, hungry and devoured
Try to silence me so I'ma scream it louder
Tell me, is it for the money or the power?
Do you do it for the money or the power?
Time to pray, we gotta
all get on our knees
Ask the Lord to heal the
land of this disease
Flippin' tables in this
dirty den of thieves
I just wanna see us all live in peace
Tell me, is it for the money or the power?
Did you do it for the money or the power?